# T.C. Rotunda

Walnut Creek, CA 94596 | tcrotunda@gmail.com | (714) 883-7973

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tcrotunda/ | GitHub: https://github.com/tcrotunda | Website: https://tcrotunda.github.io/

#### Summary

Data Specialist with 6+ years of experience working as a Business Analyst and Data Analyst for top financial firms such as JP Morgan, BNY Mellon, and Charles Schwab. Self-starter, fast learning, and can retain information at a high level. Motivated to learn new technologies. Have a passion for data, and excel in team-oriented environments. Highly detail-oriented, and able to juggle multiple projects at a time. Excellent written and verbal communication skills. Certificate in Data Analytics and Visualization through University of California, Berkeley.

## **Technical Skills**

SQL, Python, Tableau, R, VBA, AWS, JavaScript, API, MongoDB, Postgres, Hadoop, Jira, Confluence, SAP Business Objects, GitHub, GitLab, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint

#### **Employment**

Charles Schwab (Apex Systems)

San Francisco, CA

May2020 - Present

- **Business Analyst**
- Lead daily project scrum calls to ensure timely competition of user stories and appropriate allocation of resources
- Query databases using SQL to check data while conducting UAT and QA testing
- Work with developers during UAT testing to question / improve functionality and efficiencies
- Work with developers to migrate ETF trade order processing file from former vendor to new vendor
- Create documentation for import and export feeds for Aladdin trading system
- Cleanup Dealer/Branch/Issuer data for Aladdin trading system

JPMorgan Chase & Co.

New York, NY

Associate Business Data Analyst

February 2019 - June 2019

February 2016 - January 2019

- **Business Data Analyst**
- Analyzed and managed primary and secondary sourced data for the US Funds Management Data Warehouse (FMDW), specifically minimizing data errors for the Finance Team for financial reporting purposes
- Led and assisted with projects to maintain data feeds of sourced data for FMDW, and to streamline/automate/improve new downstream data feeds to other business units
- Communicated and coordinated with various lines of business, and serve as a liaison between business and technology to help improve business processes and drive changes to our ETL
- Used SAP Business Objects to query data from FMDW for analysis, reporting (daily, monthly and quarterly), UAT testing, and data quality purposes
- Maintained SAP Business Objects infrastructure and data model/data mapping for FMDW
- Worked with international teams from Europe and Asia

BNY Mellon Boston, MA

Associate Business Analyst

June 2014 - January 2016

- Maintained data and data flow for multiple systems for the Wealth Management Fixed Income trading desk
- Updated and adjusted SQL queries to find specific data for ad hoc or future needs
- Worked directly with vendor for application updates and new features to meet end user needs
- Served as a liaison between Portfolio Managers (users) and the technology group
- Helped manage and mitigate risk within the business unit

EverFi Inc. Newton, MA

Services and Curriculum Intern

June 2013 - May 2014

Performed Level-2 Technical Support and testing for technology-based education system

#### Education

### University of California, Berkeley

Berkeley, CA January 2021

Certificate in Data Analytics and Visualization

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Excel, VBA, Python, R, JavaScript, SQL Databases, Tableau, Big Data, and Machine Learning

#### Suffolk University Sawver Business School

Boston, MA

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration Management, Information Systems minor

May 2014

Awards: Magna Cum Laude | GPA: 3.77